<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0"
    xmlns:itunes="http://www.itunes.com/dtds/podcast-1.0.dtd"
    xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Alfa Coding Podcast</title>
    <itunes:owner>
        <itunes:email>arj.python@gmail.com</itunes:email>
    </itunes:owner>
    <itunes:author>Abdur-Rahmaan Janhangeer</itunes:author>
    <description>Illustrious devs and bright topics. Touches Python, freelancing, career, dev and OpenSource</description>
    <itunes:image href="https://twemoji.maxcdn.com/2/72x72/2615.png"/>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <link>https://compileralchemy.com/alfa-podcast/</link>
    
    <item>
      <title>#5. Business, The Serious Side of Python</title>
      <description>
Learn about running an MLops business with Bojan Miletic!
</description>
      <pubDate>Tue, 22 Mar 2022 20:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/alfa-podcast/5.m4a"
                 type="audio/mpeg" />
      <itunes:duration>46:34</itunes:duration>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://archive.org/download/alfa-podcast/5.m4a</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#4. The Passion For Python</title>
      <description>
Michael Driscoll has been a Python fan since the days PyPI did not yet exist. He is an author,
blogger and tinkerer. He runs PyDev of The Week. He needs no introduction. This episode
interviews Python world's interviewer!
</description>
      <pubDate>Sun, 20 Mar 2022 20:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/alfa-podcast/4.m4a"
                 type="audio/mpeg" />
      <itunes:duration>49:02</itunes:duration>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://archive.org/download/alfa-podcast/4.m4a</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#3. 14 Years Old And Teaching Typing To The World</title>
      <description>
A casual chat with the maintainer of the pypi commandline package and typesplainer.
A dive into his journey into tech and how he tackles projects. We talk along the way
of a discord.py/nextcord visual code extension, mypy from the programming interface and
a linter specifically for discord bots projects. We also get to hear the secret behind
recipe behind awesome projects!
</description>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 20:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/alfa-podcast/3.m4a"
                 type="audio/mpeg" />
      <itunes:duration>43:30</itunes:duration>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://archive.org/download/alfa-podcast/3.m4a</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#2. Knowledge Transfer in OpenSource</title>
      <description>
This podcast features two Pypy and one CPython core devs. Projects like Pypy and CPython are complex undertakings. Even to start contributing, 
people are intimidated. As maintainers of such projects, the amount of knowledge 
accumulated over the years is just huge. This episode explores the history and evoltion of Pypy.
It debunks the myth of it's difficult to contribute to Pypy. It covers efforts undertaken to
help people get initiated and progress. We also get to listen to Bahutan's own experience of 
being onboarded to the Pypy project. It also contrasts the Pypy experience with the CPython one.
You also get a lots of Pythonista gems along the way.
A dream podcast for me!
</description>
      <pubDate>Wed, 09 Mar 2022 20:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/alfa-podcast/2.mp3"
                 type="audio/mpeg" />
      <itunes:duration>1:28:55</itunes:duration>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://archive.org/download/alfa-podcast/2.mp3</guid>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>#1. Breaking Into Tech: The Traditional Way v/s OpenSource</title>
      <description>
Osmar Mansoor has had a rich career at big tech companies. Now an Engineering Manager at Amazon, 
he has been at Apple, Uber and Microsoft. Me i owe my path 100 percent to
OpenSource. The episode covers the normal break into tech path preparation as well as 
illustrates how OpenSource can be an incredible shortcut. It also covers the evolution of 
tech back then and now.
It's a breal break into tech podcast!
</description>
      <pubDate>Fri, 18 Feb 2022 20:00:00 -0000</pubDate>
      <enclosure url="https://archive.org/download/alfa-podcast/1.mp3"
                 type="audio/mpeg" />
      <itunes:duration>1:41:34</itunes:duration>
      <guid isPermaLink="false">https://archive.org/download/alfa-podcast/1.mp3</guid>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
